what's on your mind mate I am thinking
of what I have lost what your keys
arrows snacks I've got snacks cheer up
you're just a no good bully how can you
even look at yourself in the mirror I
beg your pardon I consider myself a
freedom fighter a misunderstood one when
I look at you I see pure unadulterated
chaos is it the bombs you don't like the
bombs it's so hard to tell right from
wrong if only I had someone and give me
guidance mhm someone wise and
experienced and adoptive mother if you
will oh no absolutely not doomfist Doom
fist it's a great name what's yours they
call me jrat not as
good no not as good you look like a
gentleman who eat his own toenails why
the hell would you say that to someone
just looking for something we might have
in common what's wrong man it's nothing
just beginning to think nobody likes me
maybe if you stop stealing and blowing
up everybody's stuff is it even worth it
if I don't get to do what I
[Music]
love